







Hello. I'm a UX/VX Designer & Front End Developer. I am also a Front End Developer and learning LESS to create clean and effective code. I incorporate both knowledge to create clean, beautiful and effective experience for both user and client.

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science

Web Design & Interactive Media

The Art Institute of Seattle

124 Credits in Bachelor of Arts

Animation

University of Hawaii at Manoa

Associate of Science Degree

Information in Computer Science in Network Support Leeward of Community College

## **SKILLS**

Advertising

After Effects

Axure

CSS

Flash

Github

HTML

lcon

Illustrator

InDesign

**LESS** 

Photoshop

PowerPoint

Redline

Responsive Website

**SCRUM** 

Prototyping

Web Design

Wireframing

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

From December 2016 to Current

Front End Developer

CDK Global

From September 2015 to December 2016

**UX/VX** Designer

CDK Global

From Jun 2015 to August 2015

**Graphic Designer** 

Microsoft

From March 2015 to April 2015

**Product Designer** 

Possible

From 2011 to 2015

Freelance Web Designer & Front End Developer

Strom Consulting, VMG Studio 520

From May 2012 to September 2014

Interactive Designer

Collective

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

**English** 

Advance Level

**Tagalog** 

Intermediate Level

Visayan

Mother Language